const question2 = [
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a primary element of design?",
    choice1: "Line",
    choice2: "Point",
    choice3: "Colour",
    choice4: "Plane",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "A point extended becomes a?",
    choice1: "Line",
    choice2: "Plane",
    choice3: "Volume",
    choice4: "All of the above",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a property of line?",
    choice1: "Length",
    choice2: "Surface",
    choice3: "Direction",
    choice4: "Position",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a property of plane?",
    choice1: "Length & Width",
    choice2: "Shape ",
    choice3: "Orientation",
    choice4: "Depth",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Vertical linear elements include the following except?",
    choice1: "Obelisks",
    choice2: "Dome",
    choice3: "Column",
    choice4: "Tower",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a gerneric type of plane in Architecture?",
    choice1: "Overhead Plane",
    choice2: "Wall Plane",
    choice3: "Base Plane",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a primary shape in Architecture?",
    choice1: "Circle",
    choice2: "Rectangle",
    choice3: "Triangle",
    choice4: "Square",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "All but one is not a basic posibility of grouping two or more forms?",
    choice1: "Substitution",
    choice2: "Spatial Tension",
    choice3: "Interlocking Volumes",
    choice4: "Face-to-face Contact",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "All but one is not a method of form transformation?",
    choice1: "Dimensional Transformation",
    choice2: "Subtractive Transformation",
    choice3: "Spatial Transformation",
    choice4: "Additive Transformation",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "One of the following is not configuration of path in Architecture?",
    choice1: "Linear",
    choice2: "Composite",
    choice3: "Offset",
    choice4: "Grid",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "A circulation space may not be one of the following?",
    choice1: "Enclosed",
    choice2: "Open on one side",
    choice3: "Open on both side",
    choice4: "Concentrated",
    answer: 4,
  },
];

export default question2;
